Guide to the Robert E. Lucas Papers, 1960-2004 and undated RL.00826
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Digital Material
  - World Information Foundation records, 1991-2002; 0.12 Gigabytes; 1 disk image derived from optical disk; approximately 120 megabytes.
    Scope and Contents
    Includes information about World Information Foundation (WIF), Open Research Establishment (ORE), and Scientific Discovery Newsletter from 1991-2001.